{
    "subject": "resource/I_Am_Curious_(Blue)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "I Am Curious (Blue) is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9412348866462708,
            "question": "Is 'I Am Curious (Blue)' considered a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8157009482383728,
            "question": "Can you name other films that belong to the same genre as 'I Am Curious (Blue)'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7707313299179077,
            "question": "Can you compare and contrast 'I Am Curious (Blue)' with other films in the same genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6915509104728699,
            "question": "Are there any notable directors known for making films like 'I Am Curious (Blue)'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6261345148086548,
            "question": "What genre is 'I Am Curious (Blue)' classified as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4552553594112396,
            "question": "What impact did 'I Am Curious (Blue)' have on its genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3463645875453949,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in films of this type?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2624236047267914,
            "question": "What are some of the characteristics that define a film within this genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17670798301696777,
            "question": "What makes this film stand out from others within its genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16627579927444458,
            "question": "How has the perception of this film genre changed over time?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=I Am Curious (Blue) is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6962_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes this film stand out from others within its genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6962_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the characteristics that define a film within this genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6962_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in films of this type?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6962_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6962_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6962_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6962_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6962_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6962_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6962_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6962_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6962_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6962_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6962_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information about I Am Curious (Blue), describing it as a film, including its plot, cast, style, and reception. Therefore, the triple is supported by the context information provided."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents describe \"I Am Curious (Blue)\" as a film, supporting the statement that it is a type of film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}